Guide to the Fredericka Martin Photograph Collection ALBA.PHOTO.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series IV: Addendum (2012)
  - Two Unidentified Men at Villa Paz (separated from Anne Taft correspondence, 1970), undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Unidentified Individuals (Spain), ca. 1937-1938 (Box 9, Folder 22)